#### Contact

Naogaon +8801767269929 (Mobile) avishakpodder6@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/avishakpoddar (LinkedIn) avishak.com/ (Personal)

#### Top Skills

Mobile Application Development
Project Management
Dart

# **AVISHAK PODDAR**

Android developer | Java | Blockchain | Software testing | CEO ETERCES

Rajshahi, Bangladesh

## Summary

Experienced Android developer with a track record of success in an Android studio. Skilled in Java, Android SDK, XML, APIs, Databases & Material Design. I am currently on my way to getting my BSC in computer science engineering certification.

## Experience

**ETERCES** 

Chief Executive Officer
January 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Bangladesh

Bangladesh Research & Education Network (BdREN) Internship Trainee June 2022 - July 2022 (2 months) Bangladesh

Bangladesh Army University of Engineering & Technology university management system
December 2021 - May 2022 (6 months)

Nator, Rajshahi, Bangladesh

I am developed a management software for my university with my team. Through this app we integrate university attendant, notice, assignment submission, and result systems.

### Education

Bangladesh army University of engineering & technology B.S.C in computer Engineering , Computer Engineering . (2019 - 2023)